http://www.icevest.com/privacy-policy.html

Information
How Does It Work?
Harriet Burbidge-Smith
Raw Discovery - Ride 2014 - England to Africa return in 12 days.
Online Store
Privacy Notice This site is owned and operated  by Arctic Heat USA. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost  importance to us. At Arctic Heat USA we want to make
your experience online  satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you  should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and  use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we  gather and how we use it.Information Arctic Heat USA gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information
allows us to better tailor our content to readers needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience.
Under no circumstances does Arctic Heat USA divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.Arctic Heat USA Gathers User  Information In The Following Processes: Optional Voluntary InformationWe offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary  submission of personal information by users:  1. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Arctic Heat USA gathers  the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove  themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every  newsletter that points users to the subscription management page and within  their account after logging in. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration. USAGE TRACKINGArctic Heat USA tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites.  However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual  users.Arctic Heat USA does break down overall usage statistics according to a  user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information  from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).Arctic Heat USA sometimes tracks and catalogues the search terms that users  enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs  overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.COOKIES We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of  your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information  although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information  that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal  information a cookie
can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie  can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set  your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the  warning message with each cookie. A cookie is require to allow items to be  stored in your shopping cart and to be able to check out the cart. USE OF INFORMATIONArctic Heat USA uses any information voluntarily given by our users to  enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future  content based on the interests of our users.We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on  the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think  subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Arctic  Heat USA never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties,  including advertisers,
sponsors or partners.When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users  like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what  individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This  helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms  entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters. SHARING OF THE INFORMATIONWe will not share information about individual users with any third party, except  to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the  personal safety of our users or the public.
OPT-OUT POLICYWe give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:• Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters. STORING OF FINANCIAL DATAWe do not store credit card details nor do we share details with any 3rd  parties. All transactions are through an encrypted secure connection. YOUR CONSENTBy using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information  by Arctic Heat USA. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post  those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information  we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Warranty and Returns
Privacy Policy
Product Catalogue 2020
Multiple Sclerosis Cool Vests MS Cooling Vests AustraliaCopyright 2020 - ARCTIC HEAT USA
How Does It Work?
Raw Discovery - Ride 2014 - England to Africa return in 12 days.
